watchitmade.org 2016-10-25

# Privacy policy | Watch it Made -

**In accordance with the Data Protection Act, this policy gives you information about how this website treats personal information received from our web site visitors.**

#### What is personal information?

Personal information is defined as information about you that is personally identifiable such as your name and email address. The only time we’ll use your details for any other purpose than those listed above is to email you from time to time about Watch it Made.

We respect your privacy and will not rent, sell or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies.  
Information we collect and use

We collect visitor information in the following sections of the Watch it Made web site:

Contact – if you send us an enquiry via the email form we’ll use your details to respond to your request/comments.

#### Accessing your data

You have the right to request a copy of the personal information we hold about you. Please note that, in accordance with the Data Protection Act, a £15 admin fee is applicable. For further information, please contact us using the email form.

#### Cookies

This site uses cookies to collect information about how the site is used by its visitors. Cookies provide non-personal statistical information about visits to pages on the site, which may include the duration of individual page views, paths taken by visitors through the site, and other general information. None of this information is associated with you as an individual.

However, should you wish to delete or disable the cookies, you can do so by referring to the ‘Help’ option on the menu bar of your browser. This will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies; notify you when you receive new cookies; and disable cookies altogether.  
Changes to the privacy policy

We may update this policy from time to time. Please check this page regularly for notification of any significant changes in the way we treat your personal information.

**This website is operated by:**  
EPSRC Centre for Innovative Manufacturing in Ultra Precision: Precision Engineering Institute, Building 90, Cranfield University, Bedfordshire, MK43 0AL, UK.
